Young Women's Christian Association of Greater Hartford Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Residence Records, undated, 1967-1982
  - Occupancy problem, 1982
  - Orientation, undated
  - Rates, undated
  - Residence committee, 1974-1980; (4 folders)
  - Residence materials, undated
  - Residence meetings, undated
  - Revised budget, 1982
  - Specifications of demolition of Woolverton Hall, 1971
  - Specifications of demolition of 115 Broad Street, 1968
  - “Tower Times”, undated
  - Woolverton
    - Auction, undated
    - Demolition, 1971-1972
    - History, undated
    - Minutes, undated
    - Renovation, 1970
- Series V: Camp Aya-Po, undated, 1926-1984
  - 1972-1978
  - 1974
  - 1975
  - Artesian well, undated
  - Buildings, undated
  - Buildings, grounds, equipment, undated; (2 folders)
  - Campsite information, 1926-1927
  - Conservation plan, undated
  - Dam, 1926-1962
  - General correspondence, 1965-1975
  - History, undated; (2 folders)
  - Insurance analysis, undated
  - Lease, 1983
  - Lease, 1984
  - Lightning protection, undated
  - Long range planning, 1958
  - Plumbing, 1953
  - Ranges and ovens, undated
  - Refrigerators, undated
  - Roads: inside camp, undated
  - Sale of land, undated
  - Septic tank, 1971-1972
  - Showers and shower parts, undated
  - Site analysis, undated
  - Stove, 1975
  - Tennis courts, undated
  - Use study, 1975-1976
  - Waste treatment, 1971-1972; (2 folders)
  - Water supply, undated
  - Water system, undated
  - Waterfront blueprints, 1963
  - Wiring: underground, undated
- Series VI: Programs, undated, 1967-1987
  - 1979-1980 (Box 14)
  - 1984
  - 1985, (3 folders)
  - Action Audit for Change, 1979
  - Agency overview, 1986
  - Association Review, 1975
  - Asylum Hill Community, 1972-1973
  - Career Conference, 1985
  - Career Exploration, 1978-1979
  - Child abuse, undated
  - Child Care Exchange, 1980
  - Committed to Action, undated
  - Conference, 1984
  - Curriculum/objectives, 1980
  - Displaced homemakers, 1979
  - East Granby, undated
  - Eatery, 1981
  - Eatery budget, 1982
  - Educational capability, undated
  - Fitness Center, 1982
  - Granby Youth Center, undated; (2 folders)
  - Goodwill, 1969-1974
  - Gun control, undated
  - Hartford Youth Plan, undated
  - Imperative Program, 1971
  - Intervention Project, 1976
  - Jobs Corps, 1967-1974
  - Minority Outreach Program, 1979-1980
  - Model Political Campaign Seminar, 1986
  - Music, undated
  - Need assessment, 1984
  - Neighborcare, undated; (3 folders)
  - New Jobs for Women, undated; (5 folders)
  - 120 Anniversary Committee, 1986-1987
  - Participant responsibilities, 1979
  - Plan review, 1986
  - Planning, 1986-1987; (3 folders)
  - Policies and procedures, undated
  - Program Planning committee, 1968-1973
  - Project reports, 1981-1982
  - Project Leadership, undated; (2 folders)
  - Rape Crisis service, 1974-1976
  - Regional committee, undated
  - Resumes, undated
  - Senior Services contract, undated
  - Sexual Assault Crisis Services (SACS), undated
  - Sex Equity Project, 1980-1981
  - Stop to Focus, undated
  - Suburban Women's Club, 1976-1977
  - Summer Theatre: Teenage program, 1971-1973
  - Task forces, undated
  - Teen Parent Association, undated
  - Time Out for Parents funding, 1980-1981
  - West Hartford, 1977
  - Y Wednesday, undated
  - Y Teens, undated
  - Y Teen events, 1967-1973
  - Widow-to-Widow, undated
  - Women in Leadership, 1984
- Series VII: Grants and Contracts, undated, 1945-1987
  - Capitol Region Council of Governments, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Community Renewal Team campships, 1984
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts: State funding, 1974
  - Employment Training Association contract, 1981; (2 ff)
  - Employment and Training Administration grant, 1980, 1984; (2 folders)
  - Employment and Training Administration contract, 1981-1982
  - Hartford Foundation for Public Giving, 1945-1985; (7 folders)
  - Hartford Infact grant, 1979
  - Human Resources Shelter grant, undated
  - Job Training program, 1986-1987
  - Mason fund, undated
  - New Jobs for Women, 1980, 1983
  - Office of Policy and Management grant, 1980
  - Office of Policy and Management contract, 1981; (3 ff)
  - Outreach Program grant, 1979-1980
  - Residence grants, undated
  - Robinson Foundation campships, 1980
  - Sexual Assault Crisis Center grant, 1980
  - Summer Youth Employment proposals, 1986
  - Summer Youth Employment training program, 1987; (2 folders)
  - Swindell's Charitable Foundation grant, undated
  - Time Out for Parents funding, 1983-1984; (3 folders)
- Series VIII: World Mutual Services, 1970-1982
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979
  - Endorsements, 1978
  - Films, 1979
  - Gift items, 1971-1973
  - Hartford Infact, 1978
  - Hartford area boycott endorsers, 1978-1979
  - Issues, 1981
  - Luncheons, 1980-1981; (2 folders)
  - Nestlé response to boycott and Infact advertisement, 1978-1979
  - Notes, 1974-1977
  - Publicity, 1978-1979
  - “Women I Have Known” benefit, 1981
  - World Council visitors, 1975
  - World Fellowship committee, 1970-1972
  - World Mutual Services, 1978-1982; (2 folders)
  - World Mutual Service committee, undated; (5 folders)
- Series IX: Films, undated, 1969-1976
  - 100 Anniversary Dinner, undated (Box 17)
  - Mayor's report, undated
  - “Oliver”, 1969
  - Retirement party for Ruth Thomson, 1976
  - Unidentified boxed reel, undated
  - Unidentified loose reel, undated
  - WFSB-TV service spot, undated
  - Women's activities and teen services, undated
- Series X: Scrapbooks, 1912-1983
  - Scrapbook, 1912-1915 (Box 18)
  - Scrapbook, 1927-1930
  - Campaigns book, 1912-1915
  - Camp Aya-Po, 1931
  - Scrapbook, 1935-1936
  - Tokyo YWCA, 1963
  - Welcome Wagon of Wethersfield-Rocky Hill, 1964-1965 (Box 19)
  - Newcomers Club of Wethersfield-Rocky Hill, 1970-1971
  - Newcomers Club of Wethersfield-Rocky Hill, 1971-1972
  - Newcomers Club of Wethersfield-Rocky Hill, 1975-1977
  - Newcomers Club, 1977-1978
  - Newcomers Club, 1978-1979
  - Newcomers Club, 1979-1980
  - Newcomers Club, 1982-1983 (Box 20)
  - Newcomers Club, 1980-1981
  - Newcomers Club, 1981-1982
  - Oversize Scrapbooks—Clippings
  - January 1940 - July 1945
  - July 1931 - May 1937
  - May 1937 - December 1939
  - 1905 - May 1920
  - January 1920 - December 1925
  - April 1969 - December 1970
  - January 1955 - December 1961
  - September 1967 - April 1969
  - 1970 - 1975
  - 1970 - 1973
  - January 1926 - September 1928
  - 1971 - 1973
  - Old Woolverton Hall